[{"Id":4,"Question":"If he (try) _______ harder, he (reach) _______ his goals","QuestionNumber":2,"CorrectAnswer":"tried, would reach","TopicId":14},{"Id":5,"Question":". If she (hurry / not) ________, we (miss) ________ the bus.","QuestionNumber":4,"CorrectAnswer":"does not hurry, will miss","TopicId":14},{"Id":6,"Question":"She (come) _______ to our party if she (be / not) _________ on holiday.","QuestionNumber":5,"CorrectAnswer":"would have come, had not been","TopicId":14},{"Id":7,"Question":"If you (switch) _______ on the lights, you (fall / not) ________ over the chair.","QuestionNumber":7,"CorrectAnswer":"had switched, would not have fallen","TopicId":14},{"Id":8,"Question":"It (surprise / not) _________ me if he (know / not) ________ the answer.","QuestionNumber":8,"CorrectAnswer":"would not surprise, did not know","TopicId":14},{"Id":9,"Question":"I (buy) _______ these shoes if they (fit) ________. ","QuestionNumber":10,"CorrectAnswer":"would buy, fitted","TopicId":14},{"Id":10,"Question":"The door opened ______ the man pushed. ","QuestionNumber":2,"CorrectAnswer":"because","TopicId":15},{"Id":11,"Question":"Einstein, ______ was born in Germany, is famous for his theory of relativity.","QuestionNumber":8,"CorrectAnswer":"who","TopicId":15},{"Id":13,"Question":"2x^2 - 5x + 2 = 0. В ответ записать наибольший корень, если таковые имеются. ","QuestionNumber":1,"CorrectAnswer":"4","TopicId":16},{"Id":15,"Question":"2x^2 - 5x = 0.  В ответ записать наименьший корень, если таковые имеются.","QuestionNumber":2,"CorrectAnswer":"0","TopicId":16},{"Id":16,"Question":"3x^2 - 27 = 0.  В ответ записать наименьший корень, если таковые имеются.","QuestionNumber":3,"CorrectAnswer":"3","TopicId":16},{"Id":17,"Question":"x^2 + x - 6 = 0.  В ответ записать наименьший корень, если таковые имеются.","QuestionNumber":4,"CorrectAnswer":"2","TopicId":16},{"Id":18,"Question":"x^2 - 2x - 3 = 0.  В ответ записать наименьший корень, если таковые имеются.","QuestionNumber":5,"CorrectAnswer":"3","TopicId":16},{"Id":19,"Question":"15 - 2x - x^2 = 0.  В ответ записать наименьший корень, если таковые имеются.","QuestionNumber":6,"CorrectAnswer":"3","TopicId":16},{"Id":20,"Question":"x^2 + 9x = 0.  В ответ записать наименьший корень, если таковые имеются.","QuestionNumber":7,"CorrectAnswer":"0","TopicId":16},{"Id":21,"Question":"x^2 - 7x = 0.  В ответ записать наименьший корень, если таковые имеются.","QuestionNumber":8,"CorrectAnswer":"7","TopicId":16},{"Id":22,"Question":"4x^2 - 9 = 0.  В ответ записать наименьший корень, если таковые имеются.","QuestionNumber":9,"CorrectAnswer":"1,5","TopicId":16},{"Id":23,"Question":"x^2 + 3x - 4 = 0.  В ответ записать наименьший корень, если таковые имеются.","QuestionNumber":10,"CorrectAnswer":"1","TopicId":16},{"Id":24,"Question":"Когда состоялся военный совет в Филях? ","QuestionNumber":4,"CorrectAnswer":"1 сентября 1812","TopicId":17},{"Id":25,"Question":"Когда состоялась Бородинская битва? ","QuestionNumber":5,"CorrectAnswer":"26 августа 1812","TopicId":17},{"Id":26,"Question":"Когда случилась битва под Малоярославцем?","QuestionNumber":7,"CorrectAnswer":"24 октября 1812","TopicId":17},{"Id":27,"Question":"Когда через какую реку переправлялась французская армия с 25-ого по 27-ое ноября? ","QuestionNumber":8,"CorrectAnswer":"Березина","TopicId":17},{"Id":28,"Question":"Когда французская армия пересекла Неман? ","QuestionNumber":9,"CorrectAnswer":"14 декабря 1812","TopicId":17},{"Id":29,"Question":"Сколько длилась война?","QuestionNumber":10,"CorrectAnswer":"6 месяцев и 2 дня","TopicId":17}]